Guide to the Gary P. and Sandra G. Baden Collection of Print Advertisements, 1840-1986 and undated RL.11193
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Food and Beverage, 1840-1971 and undated; 4
  - Beverages, 1891-1971 and undated; 12
    - Non-Alcoholic--Vittel, 1922-1961 (Box 29)
    - Non-Alcoholic--White Rock, 1907-1935 (Box 29)
  - Foods, 1840-1963 and undated; 13
    - Armour, 1895-1921 (Box 6)
    - Aunt Jemima, 1896-1948 (Box 6)
    - Candy (including Life Saver), 1919-1942 (Box 6)
    - Cereal, 1896-1942 (Box 6)
    - Chewing gum (Wrigley, Adams), 1918-1919 (Box 6)
    - Condiments, 1905-1952 (Box 6)
    - Cook's, 1903 (Box 6)
    - Curtiss Baby Ruth, 1928 (Box 6)
    - Egg-O-See, 1905-1907 (Box 6)
    - Heinz, 1906-1909 (Box 6)
    - Jell-O, 1908-1923 (Box 6)
    - Kellogg, 1907-1930 (Box 6)
    - Log Cabin, 1904 (Box 6)
    - Mellin's Food for the Baby, 1904-1907 (Box 6)
    - Minute Tapioca (Minute Man '76 campaign), 1918-1919 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1901-1928 (Box 6)
    - Nabisco, 1904-1916 (Box 6)
    - Necco, 1905-1907 (Box 6)
    - Nestle, 1840-1963 (Box 6)
    - Pettijohn/Quaker Oats, 1900-1927 (Box 6)
    - Pillsbury, 1891-1892 (Box 6)
    - Planter's Nuts, 1919-1921 (Box 6)
    - Post (Grape Nuts, etc.), 1907-1932 (Box 6)
    - Quaker Oats, 1897-1941 (Box 6)
    - Royal Baking Powder (also Libby), 1905-1919 (Box 6)
    - Sanitas/Kellogg Toasted Corn Flakes, 1907-1954 (Box 6)
    - Swift's Premium Ham and Bacon, 1901-1907 (Box 6)
    - Walter Baker (chocolate, cocoa; also Libby), 1901-1909 (Box 7)
    - Armour, 1944-1955 (Box 30)
    - Aunt Jemima, 1910-1935 (Box 30)
    - Campbell Soup, 1908-1946 (Box 30)
    - Candy, 1902-1955 (Box 30)
    - Carnation, 1916-1960 (Box 30)
    - Cereal, 1908-1948 (Box 30)
    - Condiments, 1904-1956 (Box 30)
    - Dairy, 1922-1944 (Box 30)
    - Flour, 1905-1944 (Box 30)
    - Fruit, 1929-1944 (Box 30)
    - Gelatin, Pudding, 1915-1942 (Box 30)
    - Heinz, 1908-1935 (Box 30)
    - Kellogg, 1910-1942 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1919-1958 (Box 30)
    - Napoleon Flour, 1912 and undated (Box 30)
    - Nestle (includes French ads), 1930-1961 (Box 30)
    - Oil, Shortening, 1915-1938 (Box 30)
    - Quaker Oats, 1901-1960 (Box 30)
    - Produce, 1920-1937 (Box 30)
    - Roquefort, 1937-1961 (Box 30)
    - Skippy Peanut Butter, 1959 (Box 30)
    - Swift's Premium Hams and Bacons, Swift's Farm and Dairy (includes soap), 1908-1930 (Box 30)
    - Tobler (chocolate), 1925-1956 (Box 30)
    - Wrigley, Swift, 1922-1943 (Box 43)
- Health and Beauty, 1883-1980 and undated; 5
  - General, 1883-1966 and undated; 14
    - Bayer aspirin (some ads in Spanish), 1917-1956 (Box 7)
    - Caswell Massey, 1909-1954 (Box 7)
    - Creams, soaps, cleansers, 1892-1951 (Box 7)
    - Creams, soaps, cleansers--Hind's, 1907-1918 (Box 7)
    - Creams, soaps, cleansers--Ivory, 1895-1934 (Box 7)
    - Creams, soaps, cleansers--Palmolive, 1937 and undated (Box 7)
    - Creams, soaps, cleansers--Pear's, 1895-1909 and undated (Box 7)
    - Johnson Johnson, 1914-1919 (Box 7)
    - Newsprint, 1924-1935 (Box 7)
    - Oral hygiene (toothpaste, mouthwash, etc.), 1907-1939 (Box 7)
    - Rubifoam, 1897-1907 and undated (Box 7)
    - Shaving products (Gillette, Mennen, Woodbury's, etc.), 1899-1935 (Box 7)
    - Squibb, 1925-1926 (Box 7)
    - Talc powder (Colgate, Mennen, etc.), 1900-1919 (Box 7)
    - Tonics and patent medicines, 1906-1920 (Box 7)
    - Baby care, 1915-1959 (Box 31)
    - Bayer, 1929-1966 (Box 31)
    - Ivory, 1915-1937 (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous, 1925-1959 (Box 31)
    - Oral Hygiene, 1911-1943 (Box 31)
    - Palmolive, 1913-1947 (Box 31)
    - Patent Medicinces Miscellaneous Toiletries, 1883-1937 (Box 31)
    - Shaving Supplies, 1900-1940 (Box 31)
    - Soap, Cleansers, 1896-1935 (Box 31)
    - Soaps, Creams, 1920-1959 (Box 31)
    - Vaseline, 1908-1914 (Box 31)
  - Cosmetics, 1903-1980; 15
    - 4711 Eau de Cologne, 1911-1957 (Box 7)
    - Bourgois, 1920-1948 (Box 7)
    - Camay, 1934-1935 (Box 7)
    - Caron, 1924-1973 (Box 7)
    - Chanel, 1947-1979 (Box 7)
    - Charles of the Ritz, 1938-1954 (Box 7)
    - Christian Dior, 1951-1959 (Box 7)
    - Ciro, 1921-1952 (Box 7)
    - Clairol, 1935-1958 (Box 7)
    - Corday, 1936-1947 (Box 7)
    - Coty, 1924-1965 (Box 7)
    - Daggett Ramsdell, 1924-1951 (Box 7)
    - Dana, 1943-1966 (Box 7)
    - D'Orsay, 1913-1953 (Box 7)
    - Djer-Kiss, 1918-1928 (Box 7)
    - Elizabeth Arden, 1925-1971 (Box 7)
    - Evyan, 1949-1963 (Box 7)
    - Germaine Monteil, 1943-1955 (Box 7)
    - Guerlain, 1914-1979 (Box 8)
    - Harriet Hubbard, 1945 (Box 8)
    - Helena Rubenstein, 1933-1959 (Box 8)
    - Houbigant, 1913-1972 (Box 8)
    - Jean D'Albret, 1954 (Box 8)
    - Jean Patou, 1962-1980 (Box 8)
    - Lancome, 1946-1959 (Box 8)
    - Lanvin, 1933-1961 (Box 8)
    - Lentheric, 1925-1957 (Box 8)
    - L'Oreal, 1924 (Box 8)
    - Lucien Lelong, 1929-1949 (Box 8)
    - Manon Lescaut, 1928 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1909-1977 (Box 8)
    - Newsprint, 1920-1947 (Box 8)
    - Nina Ricci, 1946-1976 (Box 8)
    - Piver, 1914-1928 (Box 8)
    - Prince Matchabelli, 1935-1965 (Box 8)
    - Revillon, 1927-1947 (Box 8)
    - Revlon, 1939-1958 (Box 8)
    - Rochas, 1965-1977 (Box 8)
    - Roger Gallet, 1920-1951 (Box 8)
    - Shulton (Old Spice, etc.), 1940-1949 (Box 8)
    - Weil, 1943-1947 (Box 8)
    - Woodbury, 1903-1905 (Box 8)
    - Worth, 1935-1955 (Box 8)
    - Yardley, 1920-1952 (Box 8)
    - 4711, 1904-1936 (Box 31)
    - Arys, 1919-1921 (Box 31)
    - Babani, 1922-1927 (Box 31)
    - Bourjois, 1939-1959 (Box 31)
    - Camay, Charles of the Ritz, 1929-1937 (Box 31)
    - Alexandra de Markoff, 1938-1959 (Box 31)
    - Charles of the Ritz, 1939-1948 (Box 32)
    - Ciro Pearls, 1929-1959 (Box 32)
    - Clairol, 1936-1959 (Box 32)
    - Corday, 1927-1945 (Box 32)
    - Jean Patou, 1948-1955 (Box 32)
    - Prince Matchabelli, 1932-1946 (Box 32)
    - Shulton (Old Spice), Tosca, 1930-1948 (Box 32)
    - Weil, 1934-1943 (Box 32)
    - Caron, 1926-1954 (Box 33)
    - Chanel, 1934-1976 (Box 33)
    - Coty, 1922-1965 (Box 33)
    - Cutex, 1928-1961 (Box 33)
    - Dana, D'Orsay, 1919-1954 (Box 33)
    - Elizabeth Arden, 1916-1954 (Box 33)
    - Erasmic, Gibbs, 1914-1933 (Box 33)
    - Guerlain, 1923-1961 (Box 33)
    - Helena Rubenstein, 1926-1958 (Box 34)
    - Houbigant, 1926-1956 (Box 34)
    - Isabey, 1927 (Box 34)
    - La Reine des Cremes, Lucien Lelong, 1927-1950 (Box 34)
    - Lanvin, Lentheric, 1913-1946 (Box 34)
    - L'Oreal, 1921-1923 (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous, 1896-1953 (Box 34)
    - Perfume, 1913-1937 (Box 34)
    - Pinaud, Piver, 1904-1946 (Box 34)
    - Revlon, 1937-1961 (Box 34)
    - Roger Gallet, 1926-1945 (Box 34)
    - Woodbury, Worth, 1915-1945 (Box 34)
    - Yardley, 1927-1955 (Box 34)
- Household and Other, 1895-1979; 6
  - Accessories, fixtures, hardware, 1905-1923 (Box 8)
  - Ads appearing in "Stars and Stripes", 1918-1919 (Box 8)
  - Bon Ami, 1916-1954 (Box 8)
  - Building materials, 1926-1931 (Box 8)
  - China (including Lenox), 1946-1960 (Box 8)
  - Cleaning products, 1907-1924 (Box 8)
  - Clocks, 1950-1954 (Box 8)
  - Columbia, Crescent bicycles, 1900 (Box 8)
  - Electronics, 1903-1954 (Box 8)
  - French ads, 1924-1954 (Box 8)
  - Frigidaire, Electrolux, 1927-1934 (Box 8)
  - Furniture, 1920-1933 (Box 8)
  - General Electric, 1909-1928 (Box 8)
  - Gold Dust Washing Powder, 1896-1899 (Box 8)
  - Henry Miller's Theater program (multiple ads), 1954 (Box 8)
  - Hotpoint, Rinso, Old Dutch cleanser, 1912-1924 (Box 43)
  - Kodak, 1901-1926 (Box 8)
  - L.L. Bean, 1942 (Box 8)
  - Motor boats, 1910 (Box 8)
  - Nelson Eddy program, 1936 (Box 8)
  - Office products, 1903-1951 (Box 8)
  - Office products--Mont Blanc pens, 1962-1979 (Box 8)
  - Old Dutch cleanser, 1906-1934 (Box 8)
  - Pianos, 1895-1927 (Box 8)
  - Punch magazine (multiple ads), 1926 (Box 8)
  - Silverware, 1909-1956 (Box 8)
  - Silverware--Gorham, 1902-1954 (Box 8)
  - Vacuum cleaners, 1908-1920 (Box 8)
  - Accessories, Fixtures, Hardware--Atmos Clocks, 1931-1947 (Box 35)
  - Accessories, Fixtures, Hardware--Silver, Porcelain (includes Gorham, Bing Grondahl), 1905-1955 (Box 35)
  - Appliances, 1903-1943 (Box 35)
  - Building Materials, 1911-1935 (Box 35)
  - Cleaning Products, 1915-1931 (Box 35)
  - Cleaning Products--Old Dutch/Bon Ami, 1915-1935 (Box 35)
  - Electronics, 1912-1951 (Box 35)
  - Electronics--Siemans Electric Lamps, 1922-1924 (Box 35)
  - Electronics--Sylvania, 1942-1944 (Box 35)
  - Firearms, 1904-1939 (Box 35)
  - French Ads, 1903-1937 (Box 35)
  - Frigidaire/Electrolux, 1922-1959 (Box 35)
  - Furniture, 1906-1959 (Box 35)
  - General Electric/Hotpoint, 1916-1959 (Box 35)
  - Kodak, 1922-1959 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1905-1959 (Box 35)
  - Multiple Ads per page, 1898-1934 (Box 35)
  - New Yorker, 1935 (Box 35)
  - Office Products, 1912-1960 (Box 35)
  - Piano Ads, 1906-1929 (Box 35)
  - Polaroid, 1958-1959 (Box 35)
  - Shoe Polish, 1951-1959 (Box 35)
  - Westinghouse, 1924-1947 (Box 35)
  - Endorsements--Celebrity, 1899-1971 (Box 36)
  - Endorsements--Dionne Quintuplets, 1936-1940 (Box 36)
  - Endorsements--Sports Figures, 1915-1968 (Box 36)
  - Movies, 1919-1955 (Box 36)
  - Theater, 1918-1929 (Box 36)
- Tobacco Products, 1905-1968 and undated; 7
  - Camel, 1927-1956 (Box 8)
  - Chesterfield, 1917-1957 (Box 8)
  - Lucky Strike, 1924-1942 and undated (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1906-1940 (Box 8)
  - Murad, 1905-1921 (Box 8)
  - Pall Mall, 1920-1924 (Box 8)
  - Bull Durham, Old Gold, 1930-1950 (Box 37)
  - Camel, 1931-1950 (Box 37)
  - Chesterfield, 1928-1957 (Box 37)
  - Lucky Strike, 1924-1953 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous, 1906-1963 and undated (Box 37)
  - Pall Mall, 1911-1937 (Box 37)
- Tourism and Travel, 1884-1979 and undated; 8
  - Airlines and Aircraft Companies, 1924-1970; 16
    - Air France, 1947-1970 (Box 9)
    - Air India, 1965-1968 (Box 9)
    - Alitalia/Italian Airlines, 1954-1967 (Box 9)
    - American, 1938-1958 (Box 9)
    - American, 1949-1952 (Box 43)
    - British Air/BOAC, 1947-1957 (Box 9)
    - Continental, 1959-1968 (Box 9)
    - Delta, 1941-1967 (Box 9)
    - Japan Air Lines, 1956-1963 (Box 9)
    - KLM Royal Dutch Airlines, 1944-1960 (Box 9)
    - Lufthansa, 1956-1970 (Box 9)
    - Martin Aircraft, 1946-1948 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1946-1964 (Box 9)
    - Newsprint, 1933-1951 (Box 9)
    - Northwest, 1946-1968 (Box 9)
    - Philippine Air Lines, 1952-1970 (Box 9)
    - Qantas, 1955-1964 (Box 9)
    - Sabena, 1947-1956 (Box 9)
    - Scandinavian Airlines System (SAS), 1950-1963 (Box 9)
    - SwissAir, 1953-1965 (Box 9)
    - TWA (Trans-World Airlines), 1940-1968 (Box 9)
    - United, 1935-1968 (Box 9)
    - Air France, 1939-1966 (Box 38)
    - Air India, 1949-1970 (Box 38)
    - Alitalia, Italian Airlines, 1957-1968 (Box 38)
    - American Airlines, 1937-1966 (Box 38)
    - British Air, 1925-1957 (Box 38)
    - Continental, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Iberia, 1950-1970 (Box 38)
    - Japan Air Lines, 1960-1970 (Box 38)
    - KLM Royal Dutch Airlines, 1947-1966 (Box 38)
    - Lufthansa, 1960-1970 (Box 38)
    - Martin Aircraft, 1941-1946 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1924-1965 (Box 38)
    - Philippine Air Lines, 1965-1966 (Box 38)
    - Qantas, 1956-1968 (Box 38)
    - Sabena Belgian World Airlines, 1953-1966 (Box 38)
    - Scandinavian Airline System, 1951-1966 (Box 38)
    - Swiss Air, 1962-1970 (Box 38)
    - TWA, 1937-1967 (Box 38)
    - United Airlines, 1940-1966 (Box 38)
  - Bus Lines, 1944-1947; 17
    - Bus Lines, 1944-1947 (Box 39)
  - Car Rental Services, 1958; 18
    - Car Rental Services, 1958 (Box 39)
  - Cruises and Cruise Lines, 1901-1957; 19
    - Miscellaneous, 1901-1955 (Box 9)
    - Cruise Lines, 1906-1957 (Box 39)
  - Destinations, 1898-1968 and undated; 20
    - Asia, 1933 and undated (Box 9)
    - California, 1909-1938 (Box 9)
    - California--Stanford, 1931 (Box 9)
    - Canada tour guides, undated (Box 9)
    - Cook's Tourist Advertiser, 1901 (Box 9)
    - Detroit the Beautiful (Box 9)
    - England, undated (Box 9)
    - Europe, undated (Box 9)
    - France, 1908 and undated (Box 9)
    - Hawaii, 1909-1932 (Box 9)
    - Italy, 1935 (Box 9)
    - Mexico, 1939 (Box 9)
    - Midwest U.S., 1902-1942 and undated (Box 9)
    - Monte Carlo, Sydney, Queen Mary, 1921-1938 (Box 43)
    - Montreal, undated (Box 9)
    - Northeast U.S., 1901-1945 and undated (Box 10)
    - Northwest U.S., 1909-1929 (Box 10)
    - South U.S., 1919-1941 (Box 10)
    - Sun Valley, 1937-1942 (Box 10)
    - Switzerland, 1927-1929 (Box 10)
    - The Washington Homes of Jefferson County West Virginia (Charlotte Judd Fairpairn), undated (Box 10)
    - Tourist guides and maps, 1927-1960s (Box 10)
    - Destinations, 1932-1938 (Box 39)
    - Bermuda, 1931-1935 (Box 39)
    - California (includes Pictorial California book), 1898-1943 (Box 39)
    - England, 1937-1949 (Box 39)
    - Europe, 1924-1936 (Box 39)
    - France, 1924-1937 (Box 39)
    - Hawaii, 1929-1959 (Box 39)
    - Nassau, 1946-1959 (Box 39)
    - Pacific Northwest Playground (tour guide), 1949 (Box 39)
    - Romania, 1900-1939 (Box 39)
    - Switzerland, 1924-1968 (Box 39)
    - US, Canada, Cuba, 1926-1962 (Box 39)
    - Washington, DC, undated (Box 39)
  - Hotels and Lodging, 1898-1979 and undated; 21
    - Barbizon, Chelsea, DeVere, 1931-1939 (Box 10)
    - Barclay, 1926-1936 (Box 10)
    - Benjamin Franklin, 1928-1948 (Box 10)
    - Berkshire, 1960s (Box 10)
    - Beverly, 1931-1946 (Box 10)
    - Beverly Wilshire, 1972-1979 (Box 10)
    - Book-Cadillac, 1925-1930 (Box 10)
    - Breakers, 1920-1936 (Box 10)
    - California, 1898-1977 (Box 10)
    - Canada, 1932-1954 (Box 10)
    - Carlton, 1928-1948 (Box 10)
    - Carlyle, 1939-1943 (Box 10)
    - Cavalier, 1927 (Box 10)
    - Chamberlain, 1917-1919 (Box 10)
    - Claremont, 1931-1932 (Box 10)
    - Cleveland, 1928 (Box 10)
    - Clift, 1973-1977 (Box 10)
    - Copley-Plaza, 1922-1938 (Box 10)
    - Del Monte, 1933-1935 (Box 10)
    - Delmonico, 1930s-1963 (Box 10)
    - Delmonico (and other hotels newsprint), 1913-1937 (Box 10)
    - Dorset, 1946-1967 (Box 10)
    - Drake, 1926-1979 (Box 10)
    - Ebbit, 1906-1911 (Box 11)
    - Edison, ElysĂŠe, Empire, 1909-1931 (Box 11)
    - Essex House, 1931-1957 (Box 11)
    - Gotham, 1933-1938 (Box 11)
    - Gramercy Park, 1930-1931 (Box 11)
    - Grosvenor House (London), 1929-1953 (Box 11)
    - Hilton, 1947-1963 (Box 11)
    - Hollenden, 1930-1931 (Box 11)
    - Italy, 1929-1931 (Box 11)
    - La Salle, 1923 (Box 11)
    - Lexington, Lutetia, 1920-1947 (Box 11)
    - Lombardy, 1928 (Box 11)
    - Martinique (New York), 1907-1930 (Box 11)
    - Maryland, Prince George, 1908-1927 (Box 11)
    - Mayflower, 1928-1938 (Box 11)
    - McAlpin, 1919-1948 (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1934-1954 (Box 11)
    - National Hotel Review, 1928 (Box 11)
    - Newsprint, 1915-1935 (Box 11)
    - Palmer House, 1927-1936 (Box 11)
    - Park Central, 1928-1942 (Box 11)
    - Pennsylvania, 1944 and undated (Box 11)
    - Pierre, 1931-1977 (Box 11)
    - Plaza, 1907-1938 (Box 11)
    - Regency, 1967-1978 (Box 11)
    - Ritz-Carlton, 1915-1948 (Box 11)
    - Roanoke, 1901-1928 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, 1925-1948 (Box 11)
    - Royal Alton, 1929-1930 (Box 11)
    - Santa Barbara Biltmore, 1938 (Box 11)
    - Shelton, 1925-1937 (Box 11)
    - Sheraton, 1952-1977 (Box 11)
    - Sherry-Netherland, 1937-1940 (Box 12)
    - Shoreham, 1905-1935 (Box 12)
    - St. Francis, 1931-1932 (Box 12)
    - St. Moritz, 1930-1956 (Box 12)
    - St. Regis, 1926-1960 (Box 12)
    - Stanford Court, 1973-1979 (Box 12)
    - Switzerland, 1925-1938 (Box 12)
    - The Town House, 1936-1938 (Box 12)
    - Tuscany, 1936-1974 (Box 12)
    - U.S. miscellaneous, 1906-1970 (Box 12)
    - Waldorf-Astoria, 1919-1960 (Box 12)
    - Wellington, 1930-1931 (Box 12)
    - Westbury, 1928-1950 (Box 12)
    - Young's, Parker, Tourraine, 1906-1944 (Box 12)
    - Hotels, 1919-1931 (Box 40)
    - Barclay, 1931-1932 (Box 40)
    - British, 1900-1976 (Box 40)
    - Carlton, 1926-1927 (Box 40)
    - Continental (Paris), 1926-1927 (Box 40)
    - Empire, 1909 (Box 40)
    - Essex House, 1940 (Box 40)
    - France, 1900-1931 (Box 40)
    - Grand Hotel (Paris), 1911-1928 (Box 40)
    - Hilton, 1947-1957 (Box 40)
    - The Homestead, 1934-1935 (Box 40)
    - International Miscellaneous, 1927-1948 and undated (Box 40)
    - Lexington, 1930-1955 (Box 40)
    - Lutetia (Paris), 1911-1930 (Box 40)
    - Pierre, 1932-1936 (Box 40)
    - Russell (London), 1900-1906 (Box 40)
    - Sheraton, 1949-1968 (Box 40)
    - Sherry Netherland, 1927-1946 (Box 40)
    - St. Regis, 1930-1941 (Box 40)
    - U.S., 1920-1970 (Box 40)
    - Wagram (Paris), 1925-1929 (Box 40)
    - Waldorf Astoria, 1931-1938 (Box 40)
  - Luggage, 1900-1933; 22
    - Louis Vuitton, 1921 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1900-1933 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1914-1931 (Box 40)
  - Motor Boats, 1930-1957 and undated; 23
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1957 and undated (Box 40)
  - Railroads, 1884-1949; 24
    - Miscellaneous, 1906-1940 (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous, 1884-1949 (Box 12)
- Non-advertising Materials, 1846-1974 and undated; 9
  - African Americans (advertising and non-advertising images), 1911-1935 (Box 43)
  - Canyon Kiddies (Native American caricatures), 1936 (Box 12)
  - Celebrities, war propaganda, 1917-1960s (Box 43)
  - England, 1931-1974 (Box 12)
  - England--Royalty, 1953 and undated (Box 12)
  - Fashion--Illustrations, 1893-1939 (Box 12)
  - Fashion--The Delineator, 1898-1906 (Box 12)
  - Flour/meal bags--Smelser's Own (D.P. Smelser Co., New Windsor, Md.), Old Fashioned Burr Ground Corn Meal (Damascus Milling Co., Damascus, Md.), undated (Box 43)
  - Folder from The Homestead, Hot Springs, Va., undated (Box 12)
  - Helen Wills (tennis champion), 1927 (Box 43)
  - Hotel and restaurant menus and other information, 1932 and undated (Box 12)
  - Insurance policy, American Automobile Insurance Company, 1939 (Box 13)
  - Insurance receipt and premium books (Metropolitan Life, Northwestern Mutual, Prudential), 1902-1934 (Box 13)
  - Labels, telegraphs, etc., undated (Box 13)
  - Landscape illustrations--Panama Canal, Jerusalem, International Railway Bridge (Niagara Falls), 1862-1904 (Box 43)
  - Magazine--Revista de Globo (Brazil), 1954 (Box 13)
  - Materials in French, 1923-1934 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1847-1890 and undated (Box 13)
  - Newspaper--Political, wartime, Fiorello LaGuardia, 1916-1940 (Box 43)
  - Newspaper--San Francisco Chronicle pictorial section, 1927-1939 (Box 43)
  - Portraits, 1893-1952 (Box 13)
  - Postcards, memorabilia, etc., undated (Box 13)
  - The Rider and Driver, 1905 (Box 13)
  - Theater, 1924-1934 (Box 13)
  - This Week (booklet), 1929 (Box 13)
  - African Americans in newspaper issues, 1914-1944 (Box 41)
  - African Americans in ads (includes Cream of Wheat, Gold Dust Twins), 1901-1953, 1963 (Box 41)
  - American Ambulance Hospital of Paris, 1916 (Box 41)
  - Art prints (includes ballet, Vogue magazine covers), 1922-1934 (Box 41)
  - Ephemera--Articles/Images, Roosevelt WWII, 1940-1943 (Box 41)
  - England, 1931-1957 (Box 41)
  - England--Royalty, 1900-1957 (Box 41)
  - Fashion Articles/Clippings, 1893-1957 (Box 42)
  - French Cartoons, 1918-1919 (Box 42)
  - Golden Harvest flour bag, undated (Box 42)
  - Magazine Issues--Vecko Journalen (Sweden), Sunday News (NY), 1945-1949 (Box 42)
  - Materials in French, 1846-1935 (Box 42)
  - Men Ads and Non-ad images of Men's bodies (includes Charles Atlas, Boxers), 1913-1971 (Box 42)
  - Mike's Ship-a-hoy Grotto menu, 1945 (Box 42)
  - Misc. Articles/Images (includes magazine covers), 1890-1959 (Box 42)
  - Portraits, 1923 and undated (Box 42)
  - Sheet Music--Irving Berlin "When It's Night Time Down in Dixieland", 1914 (Box 42)
  - Sheet Music--June Waldo "On the Levee", 1936 (Box 42)
  - Sheet Music--L. Wolfe Gilbert/Lewis F. Muir "Mammy Jinny's Jubilee Shake Yo Feet", 1913 (Box 42)
  - Sheet Music--Richard A. Whiting "They Made It Twice As Nice As Paradise and They Called It Dixieland", 1919 (Box 42)
  - Sheet Music--Stephen Foster "Old Black Joe with Variations" arr. E.G. Snelling, 1905 (Box 42)
  - Sheet Music--Ted Kohler/Harold Arlen "Stormy Weather", 1933 (Box 42)
  - The Great American Convertible (book), undated (Box 42)
- Newsprint Materials, 1892-1974; 10
  - Automotive--Cars and trucks, 1919-1956 (Box NP1)
  - Automotive--Petroleum products, 1919-1954 (Box NP1)
  - Automotive--Tires, 1918-1960 (Box NP1)
  - Business, 1914-1948 (Box NP1)
  - Business--Alfred Dunhill, 1928-1940 (Box NP1)
  - Business--Guaranty Trust Co., 1915-1942 (Box NP1)
  - Business--Harriman National Bank, 1913-1931 (Box NP1)
  - Business--Utility companies, 1914-1945 (Box NP1)
  - Fashion, 1921-1940 (Box NP2)
  - Fashion--Furs (including Revillon Freres), 1913-1965 (Box NP2)
  - Fashion--Menswear, 1923-1947 (Box NP2)
  - Fashion--Watches, 1939-1968 (Box NP2)
  - Food and Beverage, 1914-1950 (Box NP2)
  - Food and Beverages--Beverages, non-alcoholic--Coca-Cola, 1906-1944 (Box NP2)
  - Food and Beverage--Chewing gum, 1914-1919 (Box NP2)
  - Health and Beauty, 1892-1945 (Box NP3)
  - Health and Beauty--Bayer aspirin, 1919-1940 (Box NP3)
  - Health and Beauty--Cosmetics, 1918-1962 (Box NP3)
  - Health and Beauty--Oral hygiene, 1920-1928 (Box NP3)
  - Health and Beauty--Perfume, 1924-1962 (Box NP3)
  - Health and Beauty--Soap, cleansers, 1892-1929 (Box NP3)
  - Household and Other--Appliances, 1914-1938 (Box NP3)
  - Household and Other--Media, cinema, radio, publishing, etc., 1929-1972 (Box NP3)
  - Household and Other--Toy trains (Lionel, American Flyer, etc.), 1924-1929 (Box NP3)
  - Tobacco, 1925-1951 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--Airlines, 1931-1962 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--American Express Travel, 1919-1929 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--Cruises and cruise lines, 1923-1962 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--Destinations, 1913-1932 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--Destinations--California, 1915-1950 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--Hotels, 1913-1953 (Box NP4)
  - Tourism and Travel--Luggage, 1920-1932 (Box NP4)
  - Automotive--Cars, 1914-1940 (Box NP5)
  - Automotive--Cars, 1914-1951 (Box NP6)
  - Automotive--Petroleum products, 1917-1939 (Box NP6)
  - Automotive--Tires, 1915-1935 (Box NP6)
  - Business, 1915-1946 (Box NP7)
  - Business (including Grinnell), 1915-1930 (Box NP7)
  - Business (including J.P.Morgan), 1910s-1940s (Box NP7)
  - Business--Buildings, 1923-1932 (Box NP7)
  - Business--Department stores, 1924-1938 (Box NP7)
  - Business--Finance and insurance, 1919-1940 (Box NP7)
  - Business--Retail stores (including Abraham Straus), 1904-1948 (Box NP7)
  - Business--Utility companies, 1919-1940 (Box NP7)
  - Business--Publications advertisements, 1916-1946 (Box NP8)
  - Fashion, 1918-1936 (Box NP9)
  - Fashion (including Chanel Couture), 1928-1974 (Box NP9)
  - Fashion--Footwear, 1924-1940 (Box NP9)
  - Fashion--Watches, Louis Vuitton, 1925-1951 (Box NP9)
  - Food and Beverages--Beverages, alcoholic, 1915-1951 (Box NP9)
  - Food and Beverages--Beverages, non-alcoholic--Cliquot Club, Canada Dry and others, 1917-1934 (Box NP9)
  - Food and Beverages--Beverages, non-alcoholic--Coca-Cola, 1914-1945 (Box NP9)
  - Food and Beverages--Cheese from Switzerland, 1929-1930 (Box NP9)
  - Food and Beverages--Food, 1915-1940 (Box NP9)
  - Health and Beauty, 1917-1938 (Box NP10)
  - Health and Beauty--Bayer aspiriin, 1916-1940 (Box NP10)
  - Health and Beauty--Cosmetics, 1919-1938 (Box NP10)
  - Health and Beauty--Elizabeth Arden, Helena Rubenstein, 1925-1938 (Box NP10)
  - Health and Beauty--Woodbury and others, 1915-1928 (Box NP10)
  - Health and Beauty--Squibb, 1924-1931 (Box NP10)
  - Household and Other, 1915-1929 (Box NP11)
  - Household and Other--Appliances, 1924-1940 (Box NP11)
  - Household and Other--Movies, 1927-1938 (Box NP11)
  - Household and Other--Simmons beds, toy trains, 1919-1936 (Box NP11)